articleenclave.com 2011-06-12

# ArticleEnclave » Privacy Policy

### [Privacy Policy](http://www.articleenclave.com/privacy-policy/ "Permanent Link to Privacy Policy")

ArticleEnclave.com is an article directory website where visitors register and contribute content. We are not responsible for the content posted by visitors. We randomly check all articles and will delete them if the content is inappropriate for users.

ArticleEnclave.com may from time to time collect name, e-mail address and/or details of website visitors. This may include the content of the mailing lists, any blog comments entered or any content in any other section. These details will not be passed onto any other third party or other organization unless we are required to by government or other law enforcement authority.

If you contribute content, such as discussion comments, to the site, your contribution may be publicly displayed including personally identifiable information such as your website URL. Your e-mail will not be displayed anywhere.

ArticleEnclave.com links to independently run websites outside of the ArticleEnclave.com domain. We take no responsibility for the privacy practices or content of such web sites. 

ArticleEnclave.com is suitable for all ages, but we not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age.

Comments are welcome. However, tasteless and insulting comments may be deleted. Any personal remarks and attacks may be deleted. The same holds true for off-topic comments. Any comments that reek of link spam or marketing messages will be deleted. ArticleEnclave.com is not responsible for the content in comments other than those made by the blog authors.

ArticleEnclave.com would use the e-mail address given by the user while commenting on the blog or while signing up, to send periodic email updates. The users can unsubscribe at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the end of the newsletter emails or by using the contact us form.

This policy will be updated from time to time. If we make significant changes to this policy after that time an update will be posted oo this website. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our web site periodically.

If you feel that ArticleEnclave.com is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us using our email id – articleenclaveATgmailDOTcom
